[Female Student] Hey guys,
this creep was totally
staring at my boobs!
-(thudding)
-(students groaning)
[Male Student] Take that!
[Male Student] I can see
why you'd stare at 'em,
ya perv.
[Male Student] Yeah,
she does have a huge rack
so her boobs bounce
when she runs.
[Junpei] If I had a
button I could push
that would make
everyone I hate die,
I probably wouldn't push it.
Gross.
-Shut up, you guys.
-But, if there
was a button that would make
everyone who hated me die,
-(blood sploshing)
-(intense music)
I'd push it without hesitation.
[Junpei] Excuse me?
Excuse me?
Excuse me?!
Huh?
One adult ticket please,
for "Human Earthworm Three."
[Receptionist]
That'll be 1,800 yen.
Oh, here.
[Receptionist] Show
starts in 10 minutes.
[Junpei] Okay, thank you.
You see, I served as a
doctor for many years.
[Male Speaker] And it turned
out he had 50,000 on 'em!
-For real?
-Typical middle school brat.
-That's awesome!
-This sucks.
-A particular question.
-(people chattering)
[Junpei]
High school kids
shouldn't skip school
to watch movies.
Not that I should talk.
And that's what I realized it.
[Junpei]
(sighing) This seriously sucks.
I can't hear the movie at all.
There are always
people like these jerks,
even if they vary
to some degree.
So, you were
looking at her boobs?
I was not.
I...
-(Junpei groaning)
-(thudding)
Oh, so then you're saying
Tsubasa's lying to us?
He was definitely
looking at them.
[Male Student] Dude,
you are really asking for it.
[Male Student] Oh hey, I
just found a half off coupon.
[Male Student] Yeah, to where?
[Tsubasa] No way.
Teach him a lesson first.
[Junpei] Shit,
the girl's just using me
to see where she
stands with these guys.
And she's getting off on it.
So you were looking then.
-(thudding)
-(Junpei groaning)
(Tsubasa laughing)
[Junpei] Damn it.
I'll tell her, I'll tell her,
I'll tell her, I'll tell her!
You're not anywhere near as hot
as you think you are, Tsubasa.
And these three
all know that too.
The only reason they're
here fawning over you
is because they're hoping
you'll let them bang you!
(thudding)
And now, at last to create
the perfect human being!
She's not gonna let us bang her.
Sounds like she doesn't
even want to hang out.
[Junpei] Stop talking!
-(woman yelling)
-(phone chiming)
Dude, it's her.
[Junpei]
Turn your phone off.
Hello?
(woman screaming)
-(portal blasting)
-(screaming glitching)
(apparition chuckling)
Hey, what's up?
You three guys.
Yeah, so?
Ought to learn some manners.
(student groaning)
(blood sploshing)
[Scientist] There's
nothing to worry about.
Everything went quite well.
This is all for the creation
of the perfect human being.
-(static buzzing)
-(dissonant ambient music)
(Junpei gulping)
What the hell? (gasping)
That person I saw just now.
No, a person couldn't do that.
And if they could, would
they really be human?
What if I am the one who did it?
Are you going to condemn me now?
Were those three special to you?
Were they your friends?
[Male Student] Here you go,
I've got some
tasty lunch for ya.
-(laughing)
-(camera shuttering)
-Oh, that's harsh, man.
-Aw, poor guy.
He's all crying now.
-(laughing)
-(intense music)
(Junpei gasping)
(rain pattering)
So, can I?
Can I do that too?
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
-(sirens blaring)
-(camera shuttering)
[Officer] Get back please.
Everybody, stay back.
Yeah, we have
three male victims,
high school
students, it looks like.
(woman crying)
(suspenseful ambient music)
So, who were those two
and why were they on the
scene before forensics got there?
One of them looked
like he was just a kid.
I don't know any more
than you do so far,
but you saw the
stiffs, didn't you?
They were something else.
(dissonant ambient music)
No ordinary human
being could do that.
(man inhaling)
You just have to
pretend you never saw it,
if you want to make it to
retirement in this job anyway.
Can you see it?
This is the residual
taint of cursed energy.
No, I don't see anything.
That's because you're
not trying to see it.
We typically see curses
as if it's perfectly natural to.
When a curse technique is used,
it leaves traces behind.
That's what residuals are.
But residuals are much
fainter than cursed spirits,
so focus your vision
and look closely.
Oh, I can see them.
Of course you can.
A good sorcerer can sense
them even before seeing them.
(Yuji groaning)
Couldn't you give me a little
more praise or something?
I don't praise or
disparage anyone.
I adhere to facts and
judge on that basis.
That's who I am.
There was a time
when I mistakenly believed
society worked the same way,
but enough about that.
Let's follow them.
Yeah, all out.
No.
Moderate effort is all
that's required here.
(Yuji gasping)
Now, let's go.
[Yuji] Me and
this guy are just not clicking.
It's like I can't
get anything right.
I won't be able to
lead you this time,
but don't worry about it, kid,
'cause I've called in an
old friend you can trust.
This is Kento Nanami,
suit turned sorcerer!
Please don't ever call me that.
Plenty of Jujutsu
Sorcerers are odd balls,
but since Kento here once
worked for a corporation,
he's got a good
head on his shoulders.
Oh, he's a first
grade sorcerer too.
I doubt anyone would
appreciate an introduction like that.
[Yuji] Why do
so many of these people
wear glasses and
stuff to hide their eyes?
A company man?
Why didn't you want to
become a Jujutsu Sorcerer
from the start?
We should greet
each other first.
Nice to meet you, Itadori.
Oh, uh, yes.
Nice to meet you too.
I went to your school too,
and there, I learned one thing.
Jujutsu Sorcerers suck!
Huh?
Then I went to work
for a typical company
and learned something there too,
that having to work
for a living sucks!
[Yuji] Really?
So if both suck equally,
then I'll go with
the one I like better.
The fact is that's the
only reason I came back.
-That's dark.
-Right?
Now, Itadori, you
should understand
that I'm not at all the
same mindset as Gojo here.
I do trust him and
have great faith
in his powers and abilities,
(Satoru laughing)
but I have no respect for him!
[Satoru] Huh?!
I may hate the way
higher ups do things,
but I still believe in
rules and regulations.
This conversation's dragging on.
The point is I don't recognize
you as a sorcerer either,
but even if you
are just a vessel
for the time bomb
we know as Sukuna,
I'm hoping you can
prove yourself to be useful.
(Yuji sighing)
Lately, I've been
forced to realize
how weak and useless I am.
(somber ambient music)
But I'll become strong.
I have to get strong,
or I won't be able
to choose how I die.
Hm.
And I'm certain I
can win your respect,
but you'll see in time.
Go sell that to the higher ups,
not to me.
(gasping) Yeah, right.
Because frankly, I
don't give a damn!
Okay, I get it.
So, there wasn't anything weird
on the surveillance
cameras, right?
Right.
There was only one young
man aside from the victims.
[Yuji] Then it was
a cursed spirit?
Well, most likely.
There's a small chance the
young man could be the killer,
but we can leave him to
the police to identify as...
(rain pattering)
La, la, la, lunchbox.
No, stop.
Let me take care
of this one, Itadori.
Let's see if you can
handle the one over there.
Good detergent.
If you decide you're in
over your head, give a shout.
Why do you think
so little of me?
Give me a chance.
It's not about whether I'm
underestimating you or not.
I'm the adult here
and you're still a child.
I have a duty to prioritize
your life over my own.
I'd rather you underestimate
me than treat me like a kid.
You've faced several
life or death situations,
but that does not
make you an adult.
Realizing your hair is
falling out on your pillow,
realizing your favorite bread
has disappeared from
the convenience store,
the accumulation of those
little moments of despair in life
is what makes a person an adult.
(frenetic electronic music)
-(thunder crashing)
-(rain pattering)
My curse technique allows me
to forcibly create a weak point
I can exploit on any
opponent seven to three.
Striking the point at that ratio
when you draw a line
along the target's length
causes a critical hit.
That allows me to deal
a fair amount of damage,
even to those ranked
higher than me.
And if their cursed
energy is weak,
I can slice them in two,
even with a blunt blade.
Are you listening, Itadori?
Huh?
You were talking to me?
-(Yuji yelling)
-(thudding)
[Announcer] Home run!
-(Yuji groaning)
Should you really be revealing
something like
that to the enemy?
It's no problem to reveal
a technique like that
to an opponent.
In fact, it can even
work to your advantage--
I want to focus on the curse,
but it feels like I should
be listening to him.
There is merit to it.
Revealing one's hand
is a gambling tactic
that increases the
effectiveness of one's technique.
I'll show you.
(puddle splashing)
(creature murmuring)
(explosion blasting)
(blood sploshing)
(creature murmuring)
(blood dripping)
(blood splashing)
All of that force came from me.
Oh man.
Not only is the blade he
used completely wrapped,
but he used the back of it
to slice right
through that thing.
Behind you, Itadori.
Huh?
-(creature growling)
-(thudding)
(Yuji groaning)
I don't like you turning
your back on your opponent.
You're the one who
keeps distracting me here!
(creature growling)
(energy billowing)
[Satoru] Your cursed energy
comes up a little slow, huh?
So, what's that mean?
Your cursed energy can't keep up
with your explosive power.
You're still not good at
collecting your cursed energy,
so it lags behind.
But in effect, that creates
an irregular energy flow.
The moment after
your fist impacts,
your cursed energy slams in,
so you're creating two
impacts with every stroke.
(Yuji groaning)
(thudding)
(blood sploshing)
Divergent fist.
So sick!
It's not a skill many
sorcerers have.
This weapon will serve you well.
Hm.
[Kento] Is his
raw strength superhuman?
His initial blow has very
little cursed energy to it,
but it reaches 120% of an
average sorcerer's power.
Then the real blow of
cursed energy flows in.
It must be unimaginably
unpleasant for
those struck by it.
He has room to grow too.
If he can learn to imbue
100% of his cursed energy
into 100% of his martial arts,
now I see why Gojo
brought him to me.
Mm?
Oh, pardon me, I'll end you now.
(intense ambient music)
Itadori, wait.
Don't finish it off yet.
Have a look at this.
It's a picture I took
of my opponent.
But I thought curses didn't
show up in photographs?
Please listen to me calmly.
These creatures that
we've been fighting--
They're human.
Well, I guess I ought to
call them former humans.
They're similar to the
three from the theater.
The structure of their bodies
was forcibly altered
by a curse technique.
If that was all, I would
have noticed from the start.
The two we just fought
were more than just altered.
They were full of cursed
energy like cursed spirits are.
You'll have to ask the culprit
to explain his curse
technique to you.
Though there is evidence
their brain stems have
been tampered with,
most likely to create confusion
and impaired consciousness.
If they can tamper
with the brain,
it might be possible for
them to modify someone
to be able to use cursed energy.
The relationship
between the brain
and cursed energy is
still a black box to us.
Oh wait, is Itadori listening?
Yeah, I'm here.
I think it's important
you understand this much.
These guys died from the shock
of what happened
to their bodies,
so you didn't kill them.
Don't get the wrong
idea about that.
Thanks.
That's easy to say.
The weight of those two
deaths still feels pretty heavy.
Whatever this
thing is we're after,
it disgusts me to the core.
[Kento] This
boy can get sincerely angry
on behalf of others.
Most likely, those
residuals were a bluff
left purposely to lure us in.
Our foe is quite skilled.
It looks like this will take
more than moderate effort,
so let's go all out.
(Yuji chuckling)
Yeah.
There are cursed spirits
known as special grade
potential apparitions.
Cursed spirits are a collection
of the cursed energy
emitted by humans.
Whether it exists or not,
a shared image of
fear makes it easy
for a powerful
curse to manifest.
So, what's an example
of a shared image of fear?
You mean like monsters
and scary ghost stories?
Yes.
Like Toilet-Bound Hanako,
the Nine-Tailed Fox, and so on.
Jujutsu Sorcerers label them
special grade
potential apparitions
and keep watch for them.
And the fact that
they often categorize
powerful unidentified
curses as potential apparitions,
it makes it feel like that's
all they're focused on.
But people constantly
fear other things too,
not just those old fairytales.
Like earthquakes?
(Mahito chuckling)
I love how stress free
it can be talking to you.
Well, I don't really...
(creatures growling)
Huh?
People, the ocean,
the forests, the earth,
they fear all of them.
Because the cursed energy
directed towards those
is far too vast,
they gained wisdom
before they took shape
and they've remained
in hiding up until now.
I'm proud to call all
of them my friends.
Tell me, Mahito,
what kind of a curse are you?
Human.
I'm a curse that was born
from the hatred and fear
that people hold deep
inside toward others.
(creatures growling)
I've organized the reports
concerning recent residuals,
unnatural deaths,
and disappearances.
This should narrow down the
culprits hideout to some extent.
Oh yeah, are we storming in?
No. As I said, it's
only to some extent.
While I continue
investigating this matter,
I'd like you to handle
a different task.
This is the boy who
was at the theater,
Junpei Yoshino.
We've just determined
that he goes to the same
high school as the three victims.
Based on his actions
and the way he carries himself
in the surveillance footage,
I believe it's unlikely
that he is a curse user.
However, if he's related
to the victims in some way,
that changes things.
Curse user?
Our term for an
evil Jujutsu Sorcerer.
I've entrusted the
process to Iguchi here
and I'd like the two of you
to investigate Junpei together.
Sure.
Come to think of it,
you're the only assistant
we have as far as I know.
Well, I am the only
one of the assistants
who knows that
you're still alive.
So, here I am.
All right, that makes sense.
Let's go!
(footsteps pattering)
You don't just know the
location to some extent, do you?
You know it exactly.
Of course. If the
culprit had wanted to,
he could have left the scene
without leaving behind
any residuals at all.
It would seem we're
being lured in once again.
Weighing the risk
of storming in alone
versus taking Itadori along,
I simply made the safest choice.
He is after all still a child.
-(Iguchi groaning)
-Oh!
And hey, teacher?
Itadori!
Forgot to tell ya,
you be careful.
Itadori, I'm not a teacher
so please don't call me that.
[Yuji] So, Kento dude!
[Kento] I will slap you.
(suspenseful ambient music)
[Iguchi] There he is.
[Yuji] Huh, where's his uniform?
It looks like he hasn't been
attending school for some time.
(stoplight beeping)
We'll get out and
walk from here.
Let's go.
-(people chattering)
-(suspenseful music)
(creature murmuring)
(Closing Theme Music)
-(whimsical music)
-Juju Stroll.
Hey, Nanami.
Let's go out.
No, thank you.
No, seriously,
I have something
to talk to you about.
[Kento] Oh, that is awful.
I didn't say anything yet.
Hm.
(elegant piano music)
Hm?
(intense ambient music)
Mm.
(intense orchestral music)